http://www.paperthin.com/privacy-policy.cfm

Security
PaperThin, Inc. strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.
Usage tracking
PaperThin, Inc. does track usage patterns on our Web site and breaks down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser). However, we do not match this information with users' personally identifiable information.
Cookies
A cookie is a small data file that a Web site transfers to a user's hard drive when a user visits the Web site. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages visited. The only personal information a cookie can contain is that which a user supplies. A cookie can't read data off a hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. PaperThin does not use cookies to store passwords or any other personal information about a user.
The user may, however, elect to provide information that he wants PaperThin to remember. Users who are comfortable providing such information about themselves can access enhanced services that we cannot offer to anonymous users. Internet use of one of these services will generate a cookie containing an Account ID, so when a user later accesses the same or another service, he will not have to reenter his personally identifiable information.
